https://www.fireproductsearch.com/privacy-policy/

Fire Fighting EquipmentFFEFire Fighting HoseFirefighting Hose ReelsFire Fighting MonitorsFire Fighting NozzlesFoamClass A FoamFluorine Free FoamsProtein FoamSynthetic FoamFoam EqFoam ProportionersMobile Foam EquipmentPortable Foam EquipmentFire Vehicle AccessoriesPPVElectric Fans & BlowersLarge Fans & BlowersPetrol Fans & BlowersPPV Fan AccessoriesPumpsCompressed Air Foam Systems (CAFS)Portable Fire PumpsVehicle Mounted Fire PumpsFirefighter PPEClothingHigh Volume Pumping SuitsManaged ServicesStructural Firefighter SuitsTechnical Rescue SuitsWildland Firefighter SuitsBootsFirefighter BootsFirefighter GlovesFirefighter HoodsRescue BootsRescue GlovesFPPECommunication EquipmentFirefighter HelmetsPersonal Gas MonitorsThermal Imaging CamerasscbaBreathing Air CompressorsPPE Storage LockersSCBA SetsSCBA AccessoriesSCBA Face MasksRescue EquipmentTorchesATEX Angle TorchesATEX HandlampsATEX HeadlampsSafety TorchesRELifting BagsRescue SupportScene LightingSearch EquipmentToolsCombi ToolsCuttersPower UnitsRescue RamsSpreadersResponDecontamination UnitsFire Rescue ToolsLeak Sealing EquipmentWater RescueFire TrainingExtinguisher TrainersExtinguisher Training ModulesFire Drill TowersFire Training BuildingsFire Training PropsSmoke GeneratorsEventsSuppliers ATEX Torches & Lamps Breathing Apparatus & Compressors Fire Fighting Equipment Fire Training Firefighter Clothing Firefighter Foam Helmets, Boots & Gloves PPE Rescue Tools Search & Rescue All
ATEX Torches & Lamps
ADALIT
ATEX Torches & Lamps
Nightstick
ATEX Torches & Lamps
Peli Products
ATEX Torches & Lamps
Wolf Safety
Suppliers
Dafo Fomtec ABVideosFire FightingProduct DemosTechnical RescueVehicle Extrication TechniquesWildland FirefightingNewsEvent NewsFirefighting ArticlesIndustry NewsInterschutz NewsProduct NewsRescue ArticlesAdd Company ListingAbout UsAdvertising ContactInterschutz 2022
Home Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy by Marcus April 23, 2016This document sets out the privacy policy of Marcus Media Limited, of which fireproductsearch.com is a division (“We”/”Us” and “Our”) and explains how We use your personal information (“Your Information”).What information do we collect?When you subscribe to Us, we collect your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, user ID and password and information in relation to where you work and what kind of a job you do.We will keep a record of which products and services you are interested in. We also monitor user traffic patterns and site use.What do We do with the information?We will use the information provided by you to promote a more personal service. We are required by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679 to follow strict procedures to protect personal data.We use your personal information collected to help us:provide you with the Services set out in our terms and conditions as efficiently as possible;identify the validity of users;to allow us to contact users when required; andto allow us to mail users with information about fireproductsearch.comWe also do research on our users interests and behaviour based on the information provided to us when you subscribe to use our Services and whilst you use our Services. This research is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis.Also, We disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.Your informationWe will not pass the personal information we collect about you to any other third party.However we will disclose Your Information in a non-personal identifying form (generally in the form of statistics) to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties in order to describe our services to them and for them to analyse the use of the Website.Unsubscribing/Amending Your InformationYou can amend or remove Your Information that you give us by emailing us at any time, specifying your name, the email address/ telephone number you used to register with us and if referring to a web registration, your username in the email.Alternatively, whenever we contact you, (for example to send you an email newsletter which you have requested) you will normally find an email address at the bottom of the email, which you can use to tell us if you no longer wish to receive the newsletter or other communication in question.You can amend or update your information or personal preferences at any time, or raise comments or questions about privacy issues, by contacting us.What about “cookies”?Like many websites, We use “cookies”. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer’s hard drive by your browser. These allow Us to store your personal information (eg log-in; e-mail address; password, if relevant; areas of the Website you view) and to provide features to make your use of the Website easier. Advertisers providing adverts on our Website may also place a unique “cookie” on your browser. Most browsers allow the cookie function to be turned off. If you want to know how to do this look at the help menu on your browser.SecurityWe have taken steps to ensure that Your Information is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorised access.Business TransfersIn the unlikely event that we sell or otherwise dispose of some or all of our business to another party we reserve the right to transfer your information as part of any assets sold or disposed of. By registering on this site and consenting to these terms, you are consenting to this transfer.Transfers OverseasYour personal data may be transferred outside of the European Economic Area for processing. Any transfer of your data is done in circumstances ensuring that your data is processed only in accordance with this privacy policy and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679. By registering on this site and consenting to these terms, you are consenting to this transfer.If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement, please contact us. Share FacebookTwitterLinkedinEmail Featured Suppliers & Brands
Savox Communications
ADALIT
Holmatro Rescue Equipment
Dafo Fomtec AB
Bristol Uniforms
ESKA Gloves NewsletterSign up to the FREE Fire Product Search NewsletterLeave this field empty if you're human: Rescue Spreaders
Spreader PSP40
S 789 eWXT
SP 777 eWXT
SP 555 eWXT Latest Videos
German Fire Truck Light Show
Interior Live Fire Training Equipment
Fire Station from Erlangen explores underwater Rescue Tools
Paramedic Mountain ResponseLifting Bags
Smooth-Bore Fire Nozzle
About Fire Product SearchThe Fire Product Search website is an ever-growing international community of fire chiefs, professional firefighters, fire training officers, and trade specialists covering the field of fire fighting and rescue.With over 225,000 unique visitors each year and growing, Fire Product Search provides the latest information on fire fighting and fire rescue equipment as well as the largest and most detailed database of fire and rescue companies in the world. Facebook Twitter Instagram Linkedin Youtube EmailInformationWhy Advertise with Us?About UsCustomer FeedbackAdvertising ContactOur Other SitesIntersec 2022Interschutz 2022Fire Safety SearchMarcus MediaFollow UsFacebook
Fire Fighting EquipmentFFEFire Fighting HoseFirefighting Hose ReelsFire Fighting MonitorsFire Fighting NozzlesFoamClass A FoamFluorine Free FoamsProtein FoamSynthetic FoamFoam EqFoam ProportionersMobile Foam EquipmentPortable Foam EquipmentFire Vehicle AccessoriesPPVElectric Fans & BlowersLarge Fans & BlowersPetrol Fans & BlowersPPV Fan AccessoriesPumpsCompressed Air Foam Systems (CAFS)Portable Fire PumpsVehicle Mounted Fire PumpsFirefighter PPEClothingHigh Volume Pumping SuitsManaged ServicesStructural Firefighter SuitsTechnical Rescue SuitsWildland Firefighter SuitsBootsFirefighter BootsFirefighter GlovesFirefighter HoodsRescue BootsRescue GlovesFPPECommunication EquipmentFirefighter HelmetsPersonal Gas MonitorsThermal Imaging CamerasscbaBreathing Air CompressorsPPE Storage LockersSCBA SetsSCBA AccessoriesSCBA Face MasksRescue EquipmentTorchesATEX Angle TorchesATEX HandlampsATEX HeadlampsSafety TorchesRELifting BagsRescue SupportScene LightingSearch EquipmentToolsCombi ToolsCuttersPower UnitsRescue RamsSpreadersResponDecontamination UnitsFire Rescue ToolsLeak Sealing EquipmentWater RescueFire TrainingExtinguisher TrainersExtinguisher Training ModulesFire Drill TowersFire Training BuildingsFire Training PropsSmoke GeneratorsEventsSuppliers ATEX Torches & Lamps Breathing Apparatus & Compressors Fire Fighting Equipment Fire Training Firefighter Clothing Firefighter Foam Helmets, Boots & Gloves PPE Rescue Tools Search & Rescue All
ATEX Torches & Lamps
ADALIT
ATEX Torches & Lamps
Nightstick
ATEX Torches & Lamps
Peli Products
ATEX Torches & Lamps
Wolf Safety
Suppliers
Dafo Fomtec ABVideosFire FightingProduct DemosTechnical RescueVehicle Extrication TechniquesWildland FirefightingNewsEvent NewsFirefighting ArticlesIndustry NewsInterschutz NewsProduct NewsRescue ArticlesCopyright © 2019 Marcus Media Limited. Fire Product Search - The World's Leading Guide to Professional Fire Fighting & Rescue.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Accept Read More
